I will do a much more in-depth analysis of this Democrat-Republican hogwash, but I want
to point out though that of all the analysis that I'm seeing done, folks are failing to
realize that what we're watching are two parties who are not simply just here for the corporate,
they are here for Zionism.
And I know that some people still think that that is something that is a very specific
corner of politics, that that's like a little nudge on the side, like a little thing.
No, that is all of American politics.
And that has happened over the past 60 years with very concerted efforts.
And Zionism is a political ideology that is literally taking over the entire world and
is at the core of what is making both parties completely castrated.
Neither party is doing the thing that they actually said that they were about because
Donald Trump was always like, oh, we don't do wars.
They're doing the wars.
Democrats are like, oh, we're going to protect you.
I mean, they're not.
But if you notice, the folks behind the scenes are not just corporations.
They are also Zionists.
So if you want to get to the root, you got to get to the thing that most everybody shares.
What is the commonality that is among all of these people?
That is the root.
I'll talk to y'all later.